[
    [
        {
            "question": "Chris p. bacon. what is his nickname?",
            "answer": "Chris p. bacon.",
            "start_idx": "0",
            "end_idx": "14",
            "back_eval_a": "chris p .",
            "score": 0.8,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What is bacon s. life. chris p. bacon: my life so far?",
            "answer": "My life.",
            "start_idx": "16",
            "end_idx": "23",
            "back_eval_a": "what is bacon s life so far ? .",
            "score": 0.22222222222222224,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What has been exciting so far?",
            "answer": "My life.",
            "start_idx": "44",
            "end_idx": "51",
            "back_eval_a": "my life .",
            "score": 1.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is my age?",
                    "answer": "Just a little pigletm.",
                    "start_idx": "18",
                    "end_idx": "39",
                    "back_eval_a": "what is my age ?i am a little pigletm .",
                    "score": 0.46153846153846156,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is my age?",
            "answer": "Just a little pigletm.",
            "start_idx": "18",
            "end_idx": "39",
            "back_eval_a": "what is my age ?i am a little pigletm .",
            "score": 0.46153846153846156,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What is my name?",
            "answer": "Chris p. bacon.",
            "start_idx": "20",
            "end_idx": "34",
            "back_eval_a": "chris p .",
            "score": 0.8,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is chris p. bacon s name?",
                    "answer": "My name.",
                    "start_idx": "9",
                    "end_idx": "16",
                    "back_eval_a": "what is chris p .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is chris p. bacon s?",
                    "answer": "Funny name.",
                    "start_idx": "46",
                    "end_idx": "56",
                    "back_eval_a": "what is chris p .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is chris p. bacon?",
                    "answer": "A pig.",
                    "start_idx": "61",
                    "end_idx": "66",
                    "back_eval_a": "what is chris p .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is chris p. bacon s nickname?",
                    "answer": "You see , my name is chris p. bacon.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "36",
                    "back_eval_a": "chris bacon is his nickname .",
                    "score": 0.3076923076923077,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is chris p. bacon s name?",
                    "answer": "My name.",
                    "start_idx": "9",
                    "end_idx": "16",
                    "back_eval_a": "what is chris p .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is chris p. bacon s name?",
            "answer": "My name.",
            "start_idx": "9",
            "end_idx": "16",
            "back_eval_a": "what is chris p .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What is chris p. bacon s?",
            "answer": "Funny name.",
            "start_idx": "46",
            "end_idx": "56",
            "back_eval_a": "what is chris p .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What is chris p. bacon?",
            "answer": "A pig.",
            "start_idx": "61",
            "end_idx": "66",
            "back_eval_a": "what is chris p .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What is chris p. bacon s nickname?",
            "answer": "You see , my name is chris p. bacon.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "36",
            "back_eval_a": "chris bacon is his nickname .",
            "score": 0.3076923076923077,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What is chris p. bacon s name?",
            "answer": "I know.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "9",
            "back_eval_a": "what is chris p .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What is the beginning of this story about?",
            "answer": "The beginning.",
            "start_idx": "75",
            "end_idx": "88",
            "back_eval_a": "what is the beginning of this story about ? .",
            "score": 0.4,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the title of this story?",
            "answer": "Well , if not , let me start from the beginning.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "50",
            "back_eval_a": "the beginning is title of this story .",
            "score": 0.25,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What is my name?",
            "answer": "Maybe you 've heard of me or seen me on tv ?.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "43",
            "back_eval_a": "what is my name ? .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "Where was i taken to?",
            "answer": "The veterinarian's office.",
            "start_idx": "45",
            "end_idx": "70",
            "back_eval_a": "the veterinarian s office .",
            "score": 1.0,
            "category": [
                "setting"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a doctor?",
                    "answer": "A veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "100",
                    "end_idx": "114",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.3636363636363636,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is my first memory?",
            "answer": "My first memory.",
            "start_idx": "0",
            "end_idx": "15",
            "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
            "score": 0.375,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is a doctor?",
                    "answer": "A veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "100",
                    "end_idx": "114",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.3636363636363636,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is a doctor?",
            "answer": "A veterinarian.",
            "start_idx": "100",
            "end_idx": "114",
            "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
            "score": 0.3636363636363636,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is my first memory?",
            "answer": "The day.",
            "start_idx": "22",
            "end_idx": "29",
            "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
            "score": 0.2666666666666667,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is a doctor?",
                    "answer": "A veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "100",
                    "end_idx": "114",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.3636363636363636,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
            "answer": "Veterinarian.",
            "start_idx": "49",
            "end_idx": "61",
            "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
            "score": 0.19999999999999998,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
            "answer": "A doctor.",
            "start_idx": "118",
            "end_idx": "126",
            "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
            "score": 0.1818181818181818,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is my first memory?",
            "answer": "First.",
            "start_idx": "3",
            "end_idx": "8",
            "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
            "score": 0.14285714285714288,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is a doctor?",
                    "answer": "A veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "100",
                    "end_idx": "114",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.3636363636363636,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is my first memory?",
            "answer": "My first memory is of the day i was taken to the veterinarian 's office.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "72",
            "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
            "score": 0.8571428571428571,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is a doctor?",
                    "answer": "A veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "100",
                    "end_idx": "114",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.3636363636363636,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
            "answer": "You probably know this , but a veterinarian is a doctor who takes care of animals.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "82",
            "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
            "score": 0.6666666666666667,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a veterinarian?",
                    "answer": "Veterinarian.",
                    "start_idx": "49",
                    "end_idx": "61",
                    "back_eval_a": "a veterinarian is someone who takes care of animals .",
                    "score": 0.19999999999999998,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my first memory?",
                    "answer": "My first memory.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "15",
                    "back_eval_a": "my first memory is of the day i was taken to a veterinarian .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What was the name of dr.len?",
            "answer": "Len.",
            "start_idx": "64",
            "end_idx": "67",
            "back_eval_a": "he smelled like cinnamon .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was dr. len?",
                    "answer": "A kind-looking man.",
                    "start_idx": "35",
                    "end_idx": "53",
                    "back_eval_a": "who was dr .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "character"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who smelled like cinnamon?",
                    "answer": "Anyway , i remember being handed to a kind - looking man named dr. len who smelled like cinnamon.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "98",
                    "back_eval_a": "dr .",
                    "score": 0.1111111111111111,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "casual relationship",
                        "character"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was dr. len?",
            "answer": "A kind-looking man.",
            "start_idx": "35",
            "end_idx": "53",
            "back_eval_a": "who was dr .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "character"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "Who smelled like cinnamon?",
            "answer": "Anyway , i remember being handed to a kind - looking man named dr. len who smelled like cinnamon.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "98",
            "back_eval_a": "dr .",
            "score": 0.1111111111111111,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "casual relationship",
                "character"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What will we have together?",
            "answer": "A good life.",
            "start_idx": "88",
            "end_idx": "99",
            "back_eval_a": "a good life .",
            "score": 1.0,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "prediction"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did he look into?",
                    "answer": "My eyes.",
                    "start_idx": "15",
                    "end_idx": "22",
                    "back_eval_a": "his eyes .",
                    "score": 0.5,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did he say to mee?",
                    "answer": "He looked into my eyes and smiled and said , \" you can come home with mee , and we 'll have a good life together. \".",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "115",
                    "back_eval_a": "he said you can come home with mee and we'll have a good life together .",
                    "score": 0.8205128205128205,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "casual relationship"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did he look into?",
            "answer": "My eyes.",
            "start_idx": "15",
            "end_idx": "22",
            "back_eval_a": "his eyes .",
            "score": 0.5,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What did he say to mee?",
            "answer": "He looked into my eyes and smiled and said , \" you can come home with mee , and we 'll have a good life together. \".",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "115",
            "back_eval_a": "he said you can come home with mee and we'll have a good life together .",
            "score": 0.8205128205128205,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What happened as we drove home?",
            "answer": "That night.",
            "start_idx": "17",
            "end_idx": "27",
            "back_eval_a": "he explained something to me the past that i had been wondering about .",
            "score": 0.13333333333333336,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "outcome resolution"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is dr. len s name?",
                    "answer": "Len.",
                    "start_idx": "33",
                    "end_idx": "36",
                    "back_eval_a": "dad .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is dr. len s name?",
            "answer": "Len.",
            "start_idx": "33",
            "end_idx": "36",
            "back_eval_a": "dad .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What did dr. len explain to me as we drove home?",
            "answer": "As we drove home that night , dr. len - or dad , as i call him now - explained something to me that i had been wondering about.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "128",
            "back_eval_a": "something i had been wondering about .",
            "score": 0.3870967741935484,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What do you think your back legs don't work like?",
            "answer": "Most pigs.",
            "start_idx": "55",
            "end_idx": "64",
            "back_eval_a": "most pigs .",
            "score": 1.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is a pig?",
                    "answer": "A special pig.",
                    "start_idx": "9",
                    "end_idx": "22",
                    "back_eval_a": "a pig is unique .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is a pig?",
            "answer": "A special pig.",
            "start_idx": "9",
            "end_idx": "22",
            "back_eval_a": "a pig is unique .",
            "score": 0.5714285714285715,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is unique about you pig?",
                    "answer": "Your back legs.",
                    "start_idx": "24",
                    "end_idx": "38",
                    "back_eval_a": "it is unique because your back legs don't work like most pigs .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is unique about you pig?",
            "answer": "Your back legs.",
            "start_idx": "24",
            "end_idx": "38",
            "back_eval_a": "it is unique because your back legs don't work like most pigs .",
            "score": 0.375,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What does this say about you?",
            "answer": "Your back legs do n't work like most pigs , but that 's okay.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "61",
            "back_eval_a": "what does this say about you ? .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What is the sound of oink-oinks?",
            "answer": "Yooooo-neek.",
            "start_idx": "48",
            "end_idx": "59",
            "back_eval_a": "it is the sound of yooooo-neek .",
            "score": 0.4444444444444445,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did i think?",
                    "answer": "I thought.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "10",
                    "back_eval_a": "i like the sound of that .",
                    "score": 0.25,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does oink-oinks mean to you?",
            "answer": "The sound.",
            "start_idx": "27",
            "end_idx": "36",
            "back_eval_a": "what does oink-oinks mean to you ? .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did i think?",
                    "answer": "I thought.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "10",
                    "back_eval_a": "i like the sound of that .",
                    "score": 0.25,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did i think?",
            "answer": "I thought.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "10",
            "back_eval_a": "i like the sound of that .",
            "score": 0.25,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did i say?",
                    "answer": "Oink - oink , \" i said.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "23",
                    "back_eval_a": "what did i say ? .",
                    "score": 0.25,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does oink-oinks mean to you?",
                    "answer": "The sound.",
                    "start_idx": "27",
                    "end_idx": "36",
                    "back_eval_a": "what does oink-oinks mean to you ? .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did i say?",
            "answer": "Oink - oink , \" i said.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "23",
            "back_eval_a": "what did i say ? .",
            "score": 0.25,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What does oink-oinks mean to you?",
                    "answer": "The sound.",
                    "start_idx": "27",
                    "end_idx": "36",
                    "back_eval_a": "what does oink-oinks mean to you ? .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does oink-oinks mean to you?",
            "answer": "I like the sound of that.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "27",
            "back_eval_a": "what does oink-oinks mean to you ? .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did i think?",
                    "answer": "I thought.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "10",
                    "back_eval_a": "i like the sound of that .",
                    "score": 0.25,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "Like what animal did i squeeeeealeek with delight?",
            "answer": "Like duma.",
            "start_idx": "79",
            "end_idx": "88",
            "back_eval_a": "like duma and aspen .",
            "score": 0.6666666666666666,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What do you think the animals will be called?",
                    "answer": "My new pals.",
                    "start_idx": "65",
                    "end_idx": "76",
                    "back_eval_a": "duma and aspen .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "prediction"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is duma?",
                    "answer": "The cat.",
                    "start_idx": "90",
                    "end_idx": "97",
                    "back_eval_a": "who is duma the cat .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "character"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "When did i get excited about the new house?",
                    "answer": "When we got home.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "16",
                    "back_eval_a": "when i saw the animals .",
                    "score": 0.22222222222222224,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is duma?",
            "answer": "The cat.",
            "start_idx": "90",
            "end_idx": "97",
            "back_eval_a": "who is duma the cat .",
            "score": 0.5714285714285715,
            "category": [
                "character"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What made me squeeeeealed with delight?",
                    "answer": "All the animals.",
                    "start_idx": "27",
                    "end_idx": "42",
                    "back_eval_a": "when i saw the animals and aspen .",
                    "score": 0.4,
                    "category": [
                        "causal relationship"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "When did i get excited about the new house?",
                    "answer": "When we got home.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "16",
                    "back_eval_a": "when i saw the animals .",
                    "score": 0.22222222222222224,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What do you think the animals will be called?",
                    "answer": "My new pals.",
                    "start_idx": "65",
                    "end_idx": "76",
                    "back_eval_a": "duma and aspen .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "prediction"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did i do when we got home?",
                    "answer": "I squeeeeealed with delight.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "28",
                    "back_eval_a": "i squealed with delight .",
                    "score": 0.75,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did i do when we got home?",
                    "answer": "I squeeeeealed with delight.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "28",
                    "back_eval_a": "i squealed with delight .",
                    "score": 0.75,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What made me squeeeeealed with delight?",
            "answer": "All the animals.",
            "start_idx": "27",
            "end_idx": "42",
            "back_eval_a": "when i saw the animals and aspen .",
            "score": 0.4,
            "category": [
                "causal relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "When did i get excited about the new house?",
                    "answer": "When we got home.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "16",
                    "back_eval_a": "when i saw the animals .",
                    "score": 0.22222222222222224,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What do you think the animals will be called?",
                    "answer": "My new pals.",
                    "start_idx": "65",
                    "end_idx": "76",
                    "back_eval_a": "duma and aspen .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "prediction"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "When did i get excited about the new house?",
            "answer": "When we got home.",
            "start_idx": "0",
            "end_idx": "16",
            "back_eval_a": "when i saw the animals .",
            "score": 0.22222222222222224,
            "category": [
                "setting",
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did i do when we got home?",
                    "answer": "I squeeeeealed with delight.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "28",
                    "back_eval_a": "i squealed with delight .",
                    "score": 0.75,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did i do when we got home?",
                    "answer": "I squeeeeealed with delight.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "28",
                    "back_eval_a": "i squealed with delight .",
                    "score": 0.75,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What do you think the animals will be called?",
            "answer": "My new pals.",
            "start_idx": "65",
            "end_idx": "76",
            "back_eval_a": "duma and aspen .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "prediction"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did i do when we got home?",
                    "answer": "I squeeeeealed with delight.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "28",
                    "back_eval_a": "i squealed with delight .",
                    "score": 0.75,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did i do when we got home?",
                    "answer": "I squeeeeealed with delight.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "28",
                    "back_eval_a": "i squealed with delight .",
                    "score": 0.75,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did i do when we got home?",
            "answer": "I squeeeeealed with delight.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "28",
            "back_eval_a": "i squealed with delight .",
            "score": 0.75,
            "category": [
                "setting",
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did i do when we got home?",
                    "answer": "I squeeeeealed with delight.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "28",
                    "back_eval_a": "i squealed with delight .",
                    "score": 0.75,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did i do when we got home?",
            "answer": "And i saw all the animals that were going to be my new pals - like duma ( the cat ) and aspen ( the dog ) -.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "106",
            "back_eval_a": "i squealed with delight .",
            "score": 0.07692307692307693,
            "category": [
                "setting",
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did i do when we got home?",
                    "answer": "I squeeeeealed with delight.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "28",
                    "back_eval_a": "i squealed with delight .",
                    "score": 0.75,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "Who welcomed me with hugs and kisses?",
            "answer": "Dr. len's family.",
            "start_idx": "0",
            "end_idx": "16",
            "back_eval_a": "dr .",
            "score": 0.4,
            "category": [
                "character"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "Who welcomed me with hugs and kisses?",
            "answer": "Len.",
            "start_idx": "4",
            "end_idx": "7",
            "back_eval_a": "dr .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "character"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the first thing i noticed about dr.dr. len 's family?",
            "answer": "Dr. len 's family welcomed me with hugs and kisses , and i knew i was going to like it there !.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "94",
            "back_eval_a": "hugs and kisses .",
            "score": 0.2608695652173913,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What did i drift off to?",
            "answer": "A happy sleep.",
            "start_idx": "144",
            "end_idx": "157",
            "back_eval_a": "a happy sleep .",
            "score": 1.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What was comforting to me at the end of my long day?",
                    "answer": "The warm fire.",
                    "start_idx": "81",
                    "end_idx": "94",
                    "back_eval_a": "warm fire .",
                    "score": 0.8,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What had been the longest day of my life?",
                    "answer": "The longest day.",
                    "start_idx": "12",
                    "end_idx": "27",
                    "back_eval_a": "it had been the longest day of my life .",
                    "score": 0.5,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the longest day of my life?",
                    "answer": "My short life.",
                    "start_idx": "31",
                    "end_idx": "44",
                    "back_eval_a": "it was the longest day of my life .",
                    "score": 0.36363636363636365,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was in the pile of blankets?",
                    "answer": "Snuggly blankets.",
                    "start_idx": "108",
                    "end_idx": "124",
                    "back_eval_a": "what was in the pile of blankets ? .",
                    "score": 0.22222222222222224,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the blanket made of?",
                    "answer": "A pile.",
                    "start_idx": "98",
                    "end_idx": "104",
                    "back_eval_a": "it was made of snuggly blankets .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was comforting to me at the end of my long day?",
            "answer": "The warm fire.",
            "start_idx": "81",
            "end_idx": "94",
            "back_eval_a": "warm fire .",
            "score": 0.8,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the longest day of my life?",
                    "answer": "My short life.",
                    "start_idx": "31",
                    "end_idx": "44",
                    "back_eval_a": "it was the longest day of my life .",
                    "score": 0.36363636363636365,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was in the pile of blankets?",
                    "answer": "Snuggly blankets.",
                    "start_idx": "108",
                    "end_idx": "124",
                    "back_eval_a": "what was in the pile of blankets ? .",
                    "score": 0.22222222222222224,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the blanket made of?",
                    "answer": "A pile.",
                    "start_idx": "98",
                    "end_idx": "104",
                    "back_eval_a": "it was made of snuggly blankets .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What had been the longest day of my life?",
            "answer": "The longest day.",
            "start_idx": "12",
            "end_idx": "27",
            "back_eval_a": "it had been the longest day of my life .",
            "score": 0.5,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What was in the pile of blankets?",
                    "answer": "Snuggly blankets.",
                    "start_idx": "108",
                    "end_idx": "124",
                    "back_eval_a": "what was in the pile of blankets ? .",
                    "score": 0.22222222222222224,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the blanket made of?",
                    "answer": "A pile.",
                    "start_idx": "98",
                    "end_idx": "104",
                    "back_eval_a": "it was made of snuggly blankets .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the longest day of my life?",
            "answer": "My short life.",
            "start_idx": "31",
            "end_idx": "44",
            "back_eval_a": "it was the longest day of my life .",
            "score": 0.36363636363636365,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What was in the pile of blankets?",
                    "answer": "Snuggly blankets.",
                    "start_idx": "108",
                    "end_idx": "124",
                    "back_eval_a": "what was in the pile of blankets ? .",
                    "score": 0.22222222222222224,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the blanket made of?",
                    "answer": "A pile.",
                    "start_idx": "98",
                    "end_idx": "104",
                    "back_eval_a": "it was made of snuggly blankets .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was in the pile of blankets?",
            "answer": "Snuggly blankets.",
            "start_idx": "108",
            "end_idx": "124",
            "back_eval_a": "what was in the pile of blankets ? .",
            "score": 0.22222222222222224,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the blanket made of?",
            "answer": "A pile.",
            "start_idx": "98",
            "end_idx": "104",
            "back_eval_a": "it was made of snuggly blankets .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What did i do when it was time to go home?",
            "answer": "It had been the longest day of my short life , and i was tired , so i curled up by the warm fire in a pile of snuggly blankets and drifted off to a happy sleep.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "160",
            "back_eval_a": "i curled up by the warm fire in a pile of snuggly blankets and .",
            "score": 0.5714285714285715,
            "category": [
                "setting",
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What kind of shop did i dream about?",
            "answer": "A pie shop.",
            "start_idx": "62",
            "end_idx": "72",
            "back_eval_a": "a pie shop .",
            "score": 1.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did i dream about?",
                    "answer": "My new family.",
                    "start_idx": "26",
                    "end_idx": "39",
                    "back_eval_a": "playing with my new family and being set free in a pie shop .",
                    "score": 0.375,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did i dream about?",
            "answer": "My new family.",
            "start_idx": "26",
            "end_idx": "39",
            "back_eval_a": "playing with my new family and being set free in a pie shop .",
            "score": 0.375,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What did i dream of?",
            "answer": "I dreamed of playing with my new family and being set free in a pie shop !.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "73",
            "back_eval_a": "playing with my new family and being set free in a pie shop .",
            "score": 0.896551724137931,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What did it look like?",
            "answer": "A toy.",
            "start_idx": "141",
            "end_idx": "146",
            "back_eval_a": "it looked like a toy .",
            "score": 0.5714285714285715,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What time of day did dad show me the toy?",
                    "answer": "The morning.",
                    "start_idx": "3",
                    "end_idx": "14",
                    "back_eval_a": "morning time of day .",
                    "score": 0.3333333333333333,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was oatmeal?",
                    "answer": "A breakfast.",
                    "start_idx": "22",
                    "end_idx": "33",
                    "back_eval_a": "topped with blueberries .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What time of day did dad show me the toy?",
            "answer": "The morning.",
            "start_idx": "3",
            "end_idx": "14",
            "back_eval_a": "morning time of day .",
            "score": 0.3333333333333333,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did dad show me?",
                    "answer": "A funny-looking thing.",
                    "start_idx": "91",
                    "end_idx": "112",
                    "back_eval_a": "a toy with wheelsed .",
                    "score": 0.25,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was oatmeal?",
                    "answer": "A breakfast.",
                    "start_idx": "22",
                    "end_idx": "33",
                    "back_eval_a": "topped with blueberries .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did dad show me?",
            "answer": "A funny-looking thing.",
            "start_idx": "91",
            "end_idx": "112",
            "back_eval_a": "a toy with wheelsed .",
            "score": 0.25,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did dad think of the wheels?",
                    "answer": "It looked like a toy !.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "21",
                    "back_eval_a": "he thought it looked like a toy .",
                    "score": 0.8333333333333333,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was oatmeal?",
                    "answer": "A breakfast.",
                    "start_idx": "22",
                    "end_idx": "33",
                    "back_eval_a": "topped with blueberries .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was oatmeal?",
            "answer": "A breakfast.",
            "start_idx": "22",
            "end_idx": "33",
            "back_eval_a": "topped with blueberries .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did dad think of the wheels?",
                    "answer": "It looked like a toy !.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "21",
                    "back_eval_a": "he thought it looked like a toy .",
                    "score": 0.8333333333333333,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did dad think of the wheels?",
            "answer": "It looked like a toy !.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "21",
            "back_eval_a": "he thought it looked like a toy .",
            "score": 0.8333333333333333,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the funny looking thing with wheels?",
            "answer": "In the morning , after a breakfast of oatmeal topped with blueberries ( yum ! ) , dad showed me a funny - looking thing with wheels.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "132",
            "back_eval_a": "it looked like a toy .",
            "score": 0.07692307692307693,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What does the cart hold up?",
            "answer": "Your back legs.",
            "start_idx": "60",
            "end_idx": "74",
            "back_eval_a": "back legs .",
            "score": 0.8,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is chris s nickname?",
                    "answer": "Chris.",
                    "start_idx": "18",
                    "end_idx": "23",
                    "back_eval_a": "he is called chris .",
                    "score": 0.4,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did i say?",
                    "answer": "Oink - oink , \" i said.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "23",
                    "back_eval_a": "i said oink-oinks .",
                    "score": 0.5,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "How awesome , i thought. \"oink- oinks,\" said chris as he?",
                    "answer": "\" how awesome , i thought.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "26",
                    "back_eval_a": "he said oink-oinks .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is this for chris?",
            "answer": "A cart.",
            "start_idx": "31",
            "end_idx": "37",
            "back_eval_a": "it is a cart .",
            "score": 0.6666666666666666,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is chris s nickname?",
                    "answer": "Chris.",
                    "start_idx": "18",
                    "end_idx": "23",
                    "back_eval_a": "he is called chris .",
                    "score": 0.4,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "How awesome , i thought. \"oink- oinks,\" said chris as he?",
                    "answer": "\" how awesome , i thought.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "26",
                    "back_eval_a": "he said oink-oinks .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did i say?",
                    "answer": "Oink - oink , \" i said.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "23",
                    "back_eval_a": "i said oink-oinks .",
                    "score": 0.5,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the lady say about her cart?",
                    "answer": "I made it to hold up your back legs so you can run around and play.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "67",
                    "back_eval_a": "she said it was for chris .",
                    "score": 0.09090909090909091,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "casual relationship"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is chris s nickname?",
            "answer": "Chris.",
            "start_idx": "18",
            "end_idx": "23",
            "back_eval_a": "he is called chris .",
            "score": 0.4,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "How awesome , i thought. \"oink- oinks,\" said chris as he?",
                    "answer": "\" how awesome , i thought.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "26",
                    "back_eval_a": "he said oink-oinks .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did i say?",
                    "answer": "Oink - oink , \" i said.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "23",
                    "back_eval_a": "i said oink-oinks .",
                    "score": 0.5,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the lady say about her cart?",
                    "answer": "I made it to hold up your back legs so you can run around and play.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "67",
                    "back_eval_a": "she said it was for chris .",
                    "score": 0.09090909090909091,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "casual relationship"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did i say?",
            "answer": "Oink - oink , \" i said.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "23",
            "back_eval_a": "i said oink-oinks .",
            "score": 0.5,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the lady say about her cart?",
                    "answer": "I made it to hold up your back legs so you can run around and play.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "67",
                    "back_eval_a": "she said it was for chris .",
                    "score": 0.09090909090909091,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "casual relationship"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "How awesome , i thought. \"oink- oinks,\" said chris as he?",
                    "answer": "\" how awesome , i thought.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "26",
                    "back_eval_a": "he said oink-oinks .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did the lady say about her cart?",
            "answer": "I made it to hold up your back legs so you can run around and play.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "67",
            "back_eval_a": "she said it was for chris .",
            "score": 0.09090909090909091,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "How awesome , i thought. \"oink- oinks,\" said chris as he?",
                    "answer": "\" how awesome , i thought.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "26",
                    "back_eval_a": "he said oink-oinks .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How awesome , i thought. \"oink- oinks,\" said chris as he?",
            "answer": "\" how awesome , i thought.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "26",
            "back_eval_a": "he said oink-oinks .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What did dad put on me?",
            "answer": "The cart.",
            "start_idx": "8",
            "end_idx": "16",
            "back_eval_a": "the cart .",
            "score": 1.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What kept popping up in the air?",
                    "answer": "My wheels.",
                    "start_idx": "118",
                    "end_idx": "127",
                    "back_eval_a": "my wheels up in the air .",
                    "score": 0.5,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What kept popping up in the cart?",
                    "answer": "The air.",
                    "start_idx": "147",
                    "end_idx": "154",
                    "back_eval_a": "my wheels up in the air .",
                    "score": 0.5,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What felt strange about the cart?",
                    "answer": "The straps.",
                    "start_idx": "89",
                    "end_idx": "99",
                    "back_eval_a": "straps felt strange .",
                    "score": 0.4,
                    "category": [
                        "feeling",
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was hard to get going?",
                    "answer": "First.",
                    "start_idx": "82",
                    "end_idx": "87",
                    "back_eval_a": "it was hard to get going at first .",
                    "score": 0.2222222222222222,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was wrong with the cart?",
                    "answer": "The straps felt strange , and my wheels kept popping up in the air.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "67",
                    "back_eval_a": "it felt strange and the wheels kept popping up in air dad put me on .",
                    "score": 0.6428571428571429,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "casual relationship"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the first thing i noticed about standing up?",
                    "answer": "Dad put the cart on me , and i could stand up , but boy was it hard to get going at first.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "90",
                    "back_eval_a": "it felt strangey .",
                    "score": 0.08333333333333333,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "casual relationship"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What kept popping up in the air?",
            "answer": "My wheels.",
            "start_idx": "118",
            "end_idx": "127",
            "back_eval_a": "my wheels up in the air .",
            "score": 0.5,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What felt strange about the cart?",
                    "answer": "The straps.",
                    "start_idx": "89",
                    "end_idx": "99",
                    "back_eval_a": "straps felt strange .",
                    "score": 0.4,
                    "category": [
                        "feeling",
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was hard to get going?",
                    "answer": "First.",
                    "start_idx": "82",
                    "end_idx": "87",
                    "back_eval_a": "it was hard to get going at first .",
                    "score": 0.2222222222222222,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the first thing i noticed about standing up?",
                    "answer": "Dad put the cart on me , and i could stand up , but boy was it hard to get going at first.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "90",
                    "back_eval_a": "it felt strangey .",
                    "score": 0.08333333333333333,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "casual relationship"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What kept popping up in the cart?",
            "answer": "The air.",
            "start_idx": "147",
            "end_idx": "154",
            "back_eval_a": "my wheels up in the air .",
            "score": 0.5,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What felt strange about the cart?",
                    "answer": "The straps.",
                    "start_idx": "89",
                    "end_idx": "99",
                    "back_eval_a": "straps felt strange .",
                    "score": 0.4,
                    "category": [
                        "feeling",
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was hard to get going?",
                    "answer": "First.",
                    "start_idx": "82",
                    "end_idx": "87",
                    "back_eval_a": "it was hard to get going at first .",
                    "score": 0.2222222222222222,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What felt strange about the cart?",
            "answer": "The straps.",
            "start_idx": "89",
            "end_idx": "99",
            "back_eval_a": "straps felt strange .",
            "score": 0.4,
            "category": [
                "feeling",
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What was hard to get going?",
                    "answer": "First.",
                    "start_idx": "82",
                    "end_idx": "87",
                    "back_eval_a": "it was hard to get going at first .",
                    "score": 0.2222222222222222,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was hard to get going?",
            "answer": "First.",
            "start_idx": "82",
            "end_idx": "87",
            "back_eval_a": "it was hard to get going at first .",
            "score": 0.2222222222222222,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What was wrong with the cart?",
                    "answer": "The straps felt strange , and my wheels kept popping up in the air.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "67",
                    "back_eval_a": "it felt strange and the wheels kept popping up in air dad put me on .",
                    "score": 0.6428571428571429,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "casual relationship"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was wrong with the cart?",
            "answer": "The straps felt strange , and my wheels kept popping up in the air.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "67",
            "back_eval_a": "it felt strange and the wheels kept popping up in air dad put me on .",
            "score": 0.6428571428571429,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the first thing i noticed about standing up?",
            "answer": "Dad put the cart on me , and i could stand up , but boy was it hard to get going at first.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "90",
            "back_eval_a": "it felt strangey .",
            "score": 0.08333333333333333,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What happened after lots of practice?",
            "answer": "But after lots of practice , and with everyone cheering me on , i was rolling !.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "78",
            "back_eval_a": "i was rolling .",
            "score": 0.35294117647058826,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "outcome resolution",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What is my name?",
            "answer": "Chris.",
            "start_idx": "105",
            "end_idx": "110",
            "back_eval_a": "chris .",
            "score": 1.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What was under the couch?",
                    "answer": "A marshmallow.",
                    "start_idx": "45",
                    "end_idx": "58",
                    "back_eval_a": "marshmallow .",
                    "score": 0.6666666666666666,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What part of my body was used for filming?",
                    "answer": "My head.",
                    "start_idx": "141",
                    "end_idx": "148",
                    "back_eval_a": "my hands .",
                    "score": 0.5,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where was the marshmallow hiding under?",
                    "answer": "The couch.",
                    "start_idx": "74",
                    "end_idx": "83",
                    "back_eval_a": "under the couchy .",
                    "score": 0.4,
                    "category": [
                        "setting"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad saw me on youtube?",
                    "answer": "A few weeks later.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "17",
                    "back_eval_a": "he told me to look at it again .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened when dad shouted , look at chris?",
                    "answer": "\" i popped my head up , and sure enough , there i was !.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "54",
                    "back_eval_a": "i was on youtube .",
                    "score": 0.26666666666666666,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad saw me on youtube?",
                    "answer": "A few weeks later.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "17",
                    "back_eval_a": "he told me to look at it again .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was under the couch?",
            "answer": "A marshmallow.",
            "start_idx": "45",
            "end_idx": "58",
            "back_eval_a": "marshmallow .",
            "score": 0.6666666666666666,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What part of my body was used for filming?",
                    "answer": "My head.",
                    "start_idx": "141",
                    "end_idx": "148",
                    "back_eval_a": "my hands .",
                    "score": 0.5,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad saw me on youtube?",
                    "answer": "A few weeks later.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "17",
                    "back_eval_a": "he told me to look at it again .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened when dad shouted , look at chris?",
                    "answer": "\" i popped my head up , and sure enough , there i was !.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "54",
                    "back_eval_a": "i was on youtube .",
                    "score": 0.26666666666666666,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad saw me on youtube?",
                    "answer": "A few weeks later.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "17",
                    "back_eval_a": "he told me to look at it again .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What part of my body was used for filming?",
            "answer": "My head.",
            "start_idx": "141",
            "end_idx": "148",
            "back_eval_a": "my hands .",
            "score": 0.5,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "Where was the marshmallow hiding under?",
                    "answer": "The couch.",
                    "start_idx": "74",
                    "end_idx": "83",
                    "back_eval_a": "under the couchy .",
                    "score": 0.4,
                    "category": [
                        "setting"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad saw me on youtube?",
                    "answer": "A few weeks later.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "17",
                    "back_eval_a": "he told me to look at it again .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened when dad shouted , look at chris?",
                    "answer": "\" i popped my head up , and sure enough , there i was !.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "54",
                    "back_eval_a": "i was on youtube .",
                    "score": 0.26666666666666666,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad saw me on youtube?",
                    "answer": "A few weeks later.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "17",
                    "back_eval_a": "he told me to look at it again .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Where was the marshmallow hiding under?",
            "answer": "The couch.",
            "start_idx": "74",
            "end_idx": "83",
            "back_eval_a": "under the couchy .",
            "score": 0.4,
            "category": [
                "setting"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad saw me on youtube?",
                    "answer": "A few weeks later.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "17",
                    "back_eval_a": "he told me to look at it again .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened when dad shouted , look at chris?",
                    "answer": "\" i popped my head up , and sure enough , there i was !.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "54",
                    "back_eval_a": "i was on youtube .",
                    "score": 0.26666666666666666,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad saw me on youtube?",
                    "answer": "A few weeks later.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "17",
                    "back_eval_a": "he told me to look at it again .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What happened after dad saw me on youtube?",
            "answer": "A few weeks later.",
            "start_idx": "0",
            "end_idx": "17",
            "back_eval_a": "he told me to look at it again .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "outcome resolution"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What happened when dad shouted , look at chris?",
                    "answer": "\" i popped my head up , and sure enough , there i was !.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "54",
                    "back_eval_a": "i was on youtube .",
                    "score": 0.26666666666666666,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What happened when dad shouted , look at chris?",
            "answer": "\" i popped my head up , and sure enough , there i was !.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "54",
            "back_eval_a": "i was on youtube .",
            "score": 0.26666666666666666,
            "category": [
                "setting",
                "action",
                "outcome resolution"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad saw me on youtube?",
                    "answer": "A few weeks later.",
                    "start_idx": "0",
                    "end_idx": "17",
                    "back_eval_a": "he told me to look at it again .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What happened after dad saw me on youtube?",
            "answer": "A few weeks later , while i was trying to get a marshmallow out from under the couch , dad shouted , \" look , chris !.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "116",
            "back_eval_a": "he told me to look at it again .",
            "score": 0.13793103448275862,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "outcome resolution",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What happened when dad shouted , look at chris?",
                    "answer": "\" i popped my head up , and sure enough , there i was !.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "54",
                    "back_eval_a": "i was on youtube .",
                    "score": 0.26666666666666666,
                    "category": [
                        "setting",
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What video did dad post?",
            "answer": "My first try.",
            "start_idx": "34",
            "end_idx": "46",
            "back_eval_a": "my first try with a cart .",
            "score": 0.6666666666666666,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did dad say would not stop ringing?",
                    "answer": "The phone.",
                    "start_idx": "73",
                    "end_idx": "82",
                    "back_eval_a": "the phone would not stop ringing .",
                    "score": 0.5,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did everyone think i was?",
                    "answer": "The cutest, most bravest pig.",
                    "start_idx": "167",
                    "end_idx": "195",
                    "back_eval_a": "the cutest, braviest pig ever .",
                    "score": 0.6,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did i try first with my cart?",
                    "answer": "My cart.",
                    "start_idx": "52",
                    "end_idx": "59",
                    "back_eval_a": "what did i try first with my cart ? .",
                    "score": 0.4,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the first thing i did with my cart?",
                    "answer": "First.",
                    "start_idx": "37",
                    "end_idx": "42",
                    "back_eval_a": "i tried to push it .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did everyone think i was?",
            "answer": "The cutest, most bravest pig.",
            "start_idx": "167",
            "end_idx": "195",
            "back_eval_a": "the cutest, braviest pig ever .",
            "score": 0.6,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did dad say would not stop ringing?",
                    "answer": "The phone.",
                    "start_idx": "73",
                    "end_idx": "82",
                    "back_eval_a": "the phone would not stop ringing .",
                    "score": 0.5,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did i try first with my cart?",
                    "answer": "My cart.",
                    "start_idx": "52",
                    "end_idx": "59",
                    "back_eval_a": "what did i try first with my cart ? .",
                    "score": 0.4,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did dad post on his facebook page?",
                    "answer": "A video.",
                    "start_idx": "23",
                    "end_idx": "30",
                    "back_eval_a": "dad posted a video of my first try with the cart .",
                    "score": 0.3076923076923077,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did dad post on his facebook page?",
                    "answer": "A video.",
                    "start_idx": "23",
                    "end_idx": "30",
                    "back_eval_a": "dad posted a video of my first try with the cart .",
                    "score": 0.3076923076923077,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the first thing i did with my cart?",
                    "answer": "First.",
                    "start_idx": "37",
                    "end_idx": "42",
                    "back_eval_a": "i tried to push it .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
                    "answer": "After that , the phone would not stop ringing.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "46",
                    "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
                    "answer": "After that , the phone would not stop ringing.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "46",
                    "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after i posted the video?",
                    "answer": "I guess dad had posted a video of my first try with my cart.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "60",
                    "back_eval_a": "the phone would not stop ringinging .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution",
                        "casual relationship"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did dad say would not stop ringing?",
            "answer": "The phone.",
            "start_idx": "73",
            "end_idx": "82",
            "back_eval_a": "the phone would not stop ringing .",
            "score": 0.5,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did dad post on his facebook page?",
                    "answer": "A video.",
                    "start_idx": "23",
                    "end_idx": "30",
                    "back_eval_a": "dad posted a video of my first try with the cart .",
                    "score": 0.3076923076923077,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did dad post on his facebook page?",
                    "answer": "A video.",
                    "start_idx": "23",
                    "end_idx": "30",
                    "back_eval_a": "dad posted a video of my first try with the cart .",
                    "score": 0.3076923076923077,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did i try first with my cart?",
                    "answer": "My cart.",
                    "start_idx": "52",
                    "end_idx": "59",
                    "back_eval_a": "what did i try first with my cart ? .",
                    "score": 0.4,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the first thing i did with my cart?",
                    "answer": "First.",
                    "start_idx": "37",
                    "end_idx": "42",
                    "back_eval_a": "i tried to push it .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did i try first with my cart?",
            "answer": "My cart.",
            "start_idx": "52",
            "end_idx": "59",
            "back_eval_a": "what did i try first with my cart ? .",
            "score": 0.4,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the first thing i did with my cart?",
                    "answer": "First.",
                    "start_idx": "37",
                    "end_idx": "42",
                    "back_eval_a": "i tried to push it .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did dad post on his facebook page?",
                    "answer": "A video.",
                    "start_idx": "23",
                    "end_idx": "30",
                    "back_eval_a": "dad posted a video of my first try with the cart .",
                    "score": 0.3076923076923077,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did dad post on his facebook page?",
                    "answer": "A video.",
                    "start_idx": "23",
                    "end_idx": "30",
                    "back_eval_a": "dad posted a video of my first try with the cart .",
                    "score": 0.3076923076923077,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
                    "answer": "After that , the phone would not stop ringing.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "46",
                    "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
                    "answer": "After that , the phone would not stop ringing.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "46",
                    "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did dad post on his facebook page?",
            "answer": "A video.",
            "start_idx": "23",
            "end_idx": "30",
            "back_eval_a": "dad posted a video of my first try with the cart .",
            "score": 0.3076923076923077,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
                    "answer": "After that , the phone would not stop ringing.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "46",
                    "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
                    "answer": "After that , the phone would not stop ringing.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "46",
                    "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
                    "answer": "After that , the phone would not stop ringing.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "46",
                    "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
                    "answer": "After that , the phone would not stop ringing.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "46",
                    "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the first thing i did with my cart?",
                    "answer": "First.",
                    "start_idx": "37",
                    "end_idx": "42",
                    "back_eval_a": "i tried to push it .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the first thing i did with my cart?",
                    "answer": "First.",
                    "start_idx": "37",
                    "end_idx": "42",
                    "back_eval_a": "i tried to push it .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did dad post on his facebook page?",
            "answer": "My video.",
            "start_idx": "140",
            "end_idx": "148",
            "back_eval_a": "dad posted a video of my first try with the cart .",
            "score": 0.15384615384615385,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
                    "answer": "After that , the phone would not stop ringing.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "46",
                    "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
                    "answer": "After that , the phone would not stop ringing.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "46",
                    "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
                    "answer": "After that , the phone would not stop ringing.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "46",
                    "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
                    "answer": "After that , the phone would not stop ringing.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "46",
                    "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the first thing i did with my cart?",
                    "answer": "First.",
                    "start_idx": "37",
                    "end_idx": "42",
                    "back_eval_a": "i tried to push it .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the first thing i did with my cart?",
                    "answer": "First.",
                    "start_idx": "37",
                    "end_idx": "42",
                    "back_eval_a": "i tried to push it .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the first thing i did with my cart?",
            "answer": "First.",
            "start_idx": "37",
            "end_idx": "42",
            "back_eval_a": "i tried to push it .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
                    "answer": "After that , the phone would not stop ringing.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "46",
                    "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
                    "answer": "After that , the phone would not stop ringing.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "46",
                    "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
                    "score": 0.5714285714285715,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
            "answer": "After that , the phone would not stop ringing.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "46",
            "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
            "score": 0.5714285714285715,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "outcome resolution"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What happened after dad posted the video?",
            "answer": "It seemed like everyone had seen my video and thought i was the cutest , most bravest pig ever !.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "95",
            "back_eval_a": "my phone would not stop ringinging .",
            "score": 0.08333333333333333,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "outcome resolution",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What happened after i posted the video?",
            "answer": "I guess dad had posted a video of my first try with my cart.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "60",
            "back_eval_a": "the phone would not stop ringinging .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "outcome resolution",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What did i visit in different cities?",
            "answer": "Tv shows.",
            "start_idx": "106",
            "end_idx": "114",
            "back_eval_a": "tv shows .",
            "score": 1.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What happened after my cart?",
                    "answer": "My life.",
                    "start_idx": "9",
                    "end_idx": "16",
                    "back_eval_a": "my life got busy after that .",
                    "score": 0.5,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of my cart?",
                    "answer": "My cart.",
                    "start_idx": "74",
                    "end_idx": "81",
                    "back_eval_a": "my cart is called the name of it .",
                    "score": 0.4,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What kind of friends did i make?",
                    "answer": "All kinds.",
                    "start_idx": "144",
                    "end_idx": "153",
                    "back_eval_a": "new friends .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did i make?",
                    "answer": "New friends.",
                    "start_idx": "157",
                    "end_idx": "168",
                    "back_eval_a": "what did i make ? .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after my cart was discovered?",
                    "answer": "Everyone wated to know about me and my cart.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "44",
                    "back_eval_a": "my life got busyly .",
                    "score": 0.15384615384615383,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Where did i visit tv shows in?",
            "answer": "Different cities.",
            "start_idx": "118",
            "end_idx": "134",
            "back_eval_a": "different cities .",
            "score": 1.0,
            "category": [
                "setting"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What happened after my cart?",
                    "answer": "My life.",
                    "start_idx": "9",
                    "end_idx": "16",
                    "back_eval_a": "my life got busy after that .",
                    "score": 0.5,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of my cart?",
                    "answer": "My cart.",
                    "start_idx": "74",
                    "end_idx": "81",
                    "back_eval_a": "my cart is called the name of it .",
                    "score": 0.4,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What kind of friends did i make?",
                    "answer": "All kinds.",
                    "start_idx": "144",
                    "end_idx": "153",
                    "back_eval_a": "new friends .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did i make?",
                    "answer": "New friends.",
                    "start_idx": "157",
                    "end_idx": "168",
                    "back_eval_a": "what did i make ? .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened after my cart was discovered?",
                    "answer": "Everyone wated to know about me and my cart.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "44",
                    "back_eval_a": "my life got busyly .",
                    "score": 0.15384615384615383,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What happened after my cart?",
            "answer": "My life.",
            "start_idx": "9",
            "end_idx": "16",
            "back_eval_a": "my life got busy after that .",
            "score": 0.5,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "outcome resolution"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What kind of friends did i make?",
                    "answer": "All kinds.",
                    "start_idx": "144",
                    "end_idx": "153",
                    "back_eval_a": "new friends .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did i make?",
                    "answer": "New friends.",
                    "start_idx": "157",
                    "end_idx": "168",
                    "back_eval_a": "what did i make ? .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did my life get busy after that?",
                    "answer": "I got to visit lots of tv shows in different cities and make all kinds of new friends.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "86",
                    "back_eval_a": "my life got busy after that .",
                    "score": 0.08333333333333333,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "casual relationship"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of my cart?",
            "answer": "My cart.",
            "start_idx": "74",
            "end_idx": "81",
            "back_eval_a": "my cart is called the name of it .",
            "score": 0.4,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What kind of friends did i make?",
                    "answer": "All kinds.",
                    "start_idx": "144",
                    "end_idx": "153",
                    "back_eval_a": "new friends .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did i make?",
                    "answer": "New friends.",
                    "start_idx": "157",
                    "end_idx": "168",
                    "back_eval_a": "what did i make ? .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did my life get busy after that?",
                    "answer": "I got to visit lots of tv shows in different cities and make all kinds of new friends.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "86",
                    "back_eval_a": "my life got busy after that .",
                    "score": 0.08333333333333333,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "casual relationship"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What kind of friends did i make?",
            "answer": "All kinds.",
            "start_idx": "144",
            "end_idx": "153",
            "back_eval_a": "new friends .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What happened after my cart was discovered?",
                    "answer": "Everyone wated to know about me and my cart.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "44",
                    "back_eval_a": "my life got busyly .",
                    "score": 0.15384615384615383,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did i make?",
            "answer": "New friends.",
            "start_idx": "157",
            "end_idx": "168",
            "back_eval_a": "what did i make ? .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What happened after my cart was discovered?",
                    "answer": "Everyone wated to know about me and my cart.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "44",
                    "back_eval_a": "my life got busyly .",
                    "score": 0.15384615384615383,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "outcome resolution"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did my life get busy after that?",
                    "answer": "I got to visit lots of tv shows in different cities and make all kinds of new friends.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "86",
                    "back_eval_a": "my life got busy after that .",
                    "score": 0.08333333333333333,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "casual relationship"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What happened after my cart was discovered?",
            "answer": "Everyone wated to know about me and my cart.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "44",
            "back_eval_a": "my life got busyly .",
            "score": 0.15384615384615383,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "outcome resolution"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What did my life get busy after that?",
                    "answer": "I got to visit lots of tv shows in different cities and make all kinds of new friends.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "86",
                    "back_eval_a": "my life got busy after that .",
                    "score": 0.08333333333333333,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "casual relationship"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What did my life get busy after that?",
            "answer": "I got to visit lots of tv shows in different cities and make all kinds of new friends.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "86",
            "back_eval_a": "my life got busy after that .",
            "score": 0.08333333333333333,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What does inspring mean?",
            "answer": "People kept calling me \" inspring , \" which i think means that i make them feel like they want to do their very best.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "117",
            "back_eval_a": "makes people want to do their very best .",
            "score": 0.4666666666666667,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What does making people smile put them in?",
            "answer": "Good mood.",
            "start_idx": "138",
            "end_idx": "147",
            "back_eval_a": "good mood .",
            "score": 1.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "Who says i do that all the time?",
                    "answer": "Dad.",
                    "start_idx": "43",
                    "end_idx": "46",
                    "back_eval_a": "dad says i do that all the time .",
                    "score": 0.2222222222222222,
                    "category": [
                        "character"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who says i do that all the time?",
            "answer": "Dad.",
            "start_idx": "43",
            "end_idx": "46",
            "back_eval_a": "dad says i do that all the time .",
            "score": 0.2222222222222222,
            "category": [
                "character"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What does it seem to me that if you make people smile ,?",
                    "answer": "It seems to me that if you make people smile , it puts them in good mood.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "75",
                    "back_eval_a": "it puts them in good mood .",
                    "score": 0.5454545454545454,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does all i want to do is make people smile?",
            "answer": "All i want to do is make people smile , and dad says i do that all the time.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "76",
            "back_eval_a": "what does all i want to do is make people smile ? .",
            "score": 0.6206896551724137,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What does it seem to me that if you make people smile ,?",
            "answer": "It seems to me that if you make people smile , it puts them in good mood.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "75",
            "back_eval_a": "it puts them in good mood .",
            "score": 0.5454545454545454,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What is in a good mood?",
            "answer": "A good mood.",
            "start_idx": "17",
            "end_idx": "28",
            "back_eval_a": "it is easier to think positive .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is oinkity-oinking?",
                    "answer": "Other words.",
                    "start_idx": "123",
                    "end_idx": "134",
                    "back_eval_a": "what is oinkity-oinking ? of positive thinking .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is oinkity-oinking?",
            "answer": "Other words.",
            "start_idx": "123",
            "end_idx": "134",
            "back_eval_a": "what is oinkity-oinking ? of positive thinking .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What does this mean?",
                    "answer": "And if you 're in a good mood , it 's easier to think positive.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "65",
                    "back_eval_a": "it means you are in a good mood .",
                    "score": 0.45454545454545453,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does this mean?",
            "answer": "And if you 're in a good mood , it 's easier to think positive.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "65",
            "back_eval_a": "it means you are in a good mood .",
            "score": 0.45454545454545453,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the main point of this story?",
            "answer": "And if you think positive , who knows what you can do ?.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "54",
            "back_eval_a": "if you are in a good mood , it is easier to think positive .",
            "score": 0.33333333333333337,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What has traveling been?",
            "answer": "A great adventure.",
            "start_idx": "28",
            "end_idx": "45",
            "back_eval_a": "great adventure .",
            "score": 0.8,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the best part about traveling?",
            "answer": "Traveling all over has been a great adventure.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "46",
            "back_eval_a": "adventure .",
            "score": 0.2222222222222222,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What was delivered to my door?",
            "answer": "A hot fudge sundae.",
            "start_idx": "62",
            "end_idx": "80",
            "back_eval_a": "a hot fudge sundae .",
            "score": 1.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "Where did i stay in new york city?",
                    "answer": "A hotel room.",
                    "start_idx": "40",
                    "end_idx": "52",
                    "back_eval_a": "hotel room .",
                    "score": 0.8,
                    "category": [
                        "setting"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where did i go to stay?",
                    "answer": "New york city.",
                    "start_idx": "15",
                    "end_idx": "28",
                    "back_eval_a": "hotel .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "setting"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Where was the hot fudge sundae delivered to?",
            "answer": "My door.",
            "start_idx": "94",
            "end_idx": "101",
            "back_eval_a": "my door .",
            "score": 1.0,
            "category": [
                "setting"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "Where did i stay in new york city?",
                    "answer": "A hotel room.",
                    "start_idx": "40",
                    "end_idx": "52",
                    "back_eval_a": "hotel room .",
                    "score": 0.8,
                    "category": [
                        "setting"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where did i go to stay?",
                    "answer": "New york city.",
                    "start_idx": "15",
                    "end_idx": "28",
                    "back_eval_a": "hotel .",
                    "score": 0.0,
                    "category": [
                        "setting"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Where did i stay in new york city?",
            "answer": "A hotel room.",
            "start_idx": "40",
            "end_idx": "52",
            "back_eval_a": "hotel room .",
            "score": 0.8,
            "category": [
                "setting"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "Where did i go to stay?",
            "answer": "New york city.",
            "start_idx": "15",
            "end_idx": "28",
            "back_eval_a": "hotel .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "setting"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What did i do in new york city?",
            "answer": "I even went to new york city , stayed in a hotel room , and had a hot fudge sundae delivered to my door !.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "104",
            "back_eval_a": "stayed in a hotel room and had hot fudge sundae delivered to my door .",
            "score": 0.7777777777777778,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What is most important to you?",
            "answer": "My family.",
            "start_idx": "84",
            "end_idx": "93",
            "back_eval_a": "being with your family .",
            "score": 0.3333333333333333,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the main thing that you are happy about being famous for?",
                    "answer": "Being famous is all really fun and exciting , but now i 'm happy to be back home with my family , playing with aspen and duma and getting as dirty as possible.",
                    "start_idx": "-1",
                    "end_idx": "159",
                    "back_eval_a": "being with your family .",
                    "score": 0.1714285714285714,
                    "category": [
                        "action",
                        "casual relationship"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the main thing that you are happy about being famous for?",
            "answer": "Being famous is all really fun and exciting , but now i 'm happy to be back home with my family , playing with aspen and duma and getting as dirty as possible.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "159",
            "back_eval_a": "being with your family .",
            "score": 0.1714285714285714,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What is the best thing about my new life?",
            "answer": "The best thing.",
            "start_idx": "0",
            "end_idx": "14",
            "back_eval_a": "i get to meet people and animals who are different .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the best thing about my new life?",
            "answer": "My new life.",
            "start_idx": "21",
            "end_idx": "32",
            "back_eval_a": "i get to meet people and animals who are different .",
            "score": 0.0,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the best thing about my new life?",
            "answer": "The best thing about my new life is that i get to meet people and animals who are different.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "94",
            "back_eval_a": "i get to meet people and animals who are different .",
            "score": 0.6896551724137931,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "What does the story show that helps kids learn to be yooooo-neek?",
            "answer": "A tiny pink pig.",
            "start_idx": "32",
            "end_idx": "47",
            "back_eval_a": "what a tiny pink pig can do help .",
            "score": 0.6666666666666666,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What do they realize that piggies can also be?",
                    "answer": "All kinds.",
                    "start_idx": "139",
                    "end_idx": "148",
                    "back_eval_a": "all kinds of things .",
                    "score": 0.6666666666666666,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What do they realize that piggies can also be?",
            "answer": "All kinds.",
            "start_idx": "139",
            "end_idx": "148",
            "back_eval_a": "all kinds of things .",
            "score": 0.6666666666666666,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the pink pig need?",
                    "answer": "A little help.",
                    "start_idx": "60",
                    "end_idx": "73",
                    "back_eval_a": "what does the pink pig need ? a little help .",
                    "score": 0.5,
                    "category": [
                        "action"
                    ],
                    "answer_in_text": true
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the pink pig need?",
            "answer": "A little help.",
            "start_idx": "60",
            "end_idx": "73",
            "back_eval_a": "what does the pink pig need ? a little help .",
            "score": 0.5,
            "category": [
                "action"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": true,
            "follow_ups": []
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the pink pig show that kids can do?",
            "answer": "I think that when they see what a tiny pink pig can do with a little help - and a lot of grunting - it makes them realize that they can do all kinds of things , too.",
            "start_idx": "-1",
            "end_idx": "165",
            "back_eval_a": "what kids can do with a little help and gruntingng .",
            "score": 0.3555555555555555,
            "category": [
                "action",
                "casual relationship"
            ],
            "answer_in_text": false,
            "follow_ups": []
        }
    ]
]